[{"question": " hey, wouldn't be cool if our duck and chick had a little baby? we could call it chuck.", "answer": " or... dick.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": "  hey. chandler and joey: hey.", "answer": " listen, i-i need a favor. umm, i was in the shower, and as i was cleansing myself, i ah, i-i, well i felt something.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " was it like a sneeze only better?", "answer": " no, no, i mean, i mean a thing on my body.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": "  what was it?", "answer": " well, i don't know, it's-it's kinda in a place that's not... it's not visually accessible to me, and i was hoping maybe you guys could-could help me out.  chandler and joey: whoa!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " no!!", "answer": " come on you guys, it's no big deal!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " whoa-heeeiiiiii-iiiii-ah!!  huh.", "answer": " well what is it? is it a mole?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " no, it's too wrinkly to be a mole.", "answer": " well, eww. what? is it a pimple?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " no, it's... fancier than a pimple. look ross, why don't you just go see a\u009a", "answer": "  hey guys! what's...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " okay, well, it's definite, two more weeks of winter.", "answer": " ahhh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " good deal.", "answer": " yeah, and these are my friends. people. this is vince, vince the people.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " vince is a fireman.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " wow! have you ever rescued anyone from a burning building before?", "answer": " 98 hot saves, highest in the force.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " well, y'know if joey and i played with matches we could get you up to an even hundred.", "answer": "  fire safety is not a joke, son.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " you're right, i know.", "answer": "  look, i gotta go. i'm on call tonight.  see you saturday.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " wow, he's cute, pheebs! but i thought you just started dating that kindergarten teacher.", "answer": " oh, jason? yeah, uh-huh, we're seeing each other tonight.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " what-pheebs?! two dates in one day? that's so unlike you.", "answer": " i know, i know! i'm like playing the field. y'know? like, juggling two guys, i'm sowing my wild oats. y'know? y'know, this kind've like y'know oat-sowin', field-playin' juggler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " so pheebs, do they know about each other?", "answer": " does a dog's lips move when he reads?  okay, no they don't.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": "  hey guys!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": "  well?!", "answer": "  okay, how'd it go at the doctor's?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " well, he said there's definitely nothing to worry about, it's totally benign.", "answer": " well what is it?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " he couldn't even tell me! he said it was just some sort of skin... abnormality. and the worst thing is he-he-he said, he said, without being able to identify it, he was reluctant to remove it.", "answer": " y'know what? you should go to my guy, because when i went in there with my third nipple. he just lopped it right off. y'know? so i guess i'm lucky. i mean not as lucky as people who were born with two nipples.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " at least they knew what yours was. y'know, yours had a name.", "answer": " oh! maybe they'll name yours after you! y'know, they'll call it, the ross. and then people would be like, \"awww, he's got a ross.\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " pete's breaking up with me.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " i just checked my messages, and he said that when he gets back from atlanta, we need to talk.", "answer": " and?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " well that's it. people never say `we need to talk' unless it's something bad.", "answer": " whoa, that doesn't necessarily mean that he's breaking up with you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " really?!", "answer": " yeah, maybe he just cheated on you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " ...and i know i'll never miss doing it, but i gotta tell you, it's pretty cool knowing that you're making a difference in a kid's life.", "answer": " that is so great! oh, i...  oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " whoa!", "answer": "  oh my god!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " ahh-ahh, we'd better call the fire department!", "answer": "  no! no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " no, no?", "answer": " well, we don't n-n-n-n-need a fireman, we'd, we'd like a good mechanic.  oh my god, here they come! well, we gotta get out of here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " w-w-w-wait! why?!", "answer": " well look, if i wanted to see a fireman, i would date one. okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " th-th-that's all it is, a third nipple. y'know? just your run-of-the-mill third nipple. y'know? you can take it off. just slice that baby right off!", "answer": " take your shirt off, and let's see what we're dealing with here.  what are you doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " just showing you my run-of-the-mill-slice-it-right-off third nipple.", "answer": " well that's not a third nipple.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " no?", "answer": " first of all, it's on your ass.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " well then, what is it?!", "answer": " wait a minute, hold it.  johnson! will you come in here a moment?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " i'm with hamilton!", "answer": " he's good with rear things, bring him in too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": "  i gotta go water pete's plants.  y'know what, if he's gonna break up with me, maybe i won't water his plants.", "answer": " well, if he's gonna break up with you, maybe joey and i should water his plants. if y'know what i mean.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " or ha-ha, we could go over there and pee on them.", "answer": "  \u009aand i-i can't take it! y'know? i'm just, always afraid one of them is gonna catch me with the other one. it's making me crazy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " well honey, then why don't you break up with one of them?", "answer": "  uh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " whoa-whoa-whoa. what ah, what happened to playing the field?", "answer": " well, it just, it doesn't feel like playing anymore, it feels like work. it's like i'm working in the field.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " so pheebs, pick one of them.", "answer": " yeah. which one do you like more?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " okay, good, so there you go. go with vince.", "answer": " yeah, but jason's really sensitive.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " well sensitive is important, pick him.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " oh sure, go with the sissy.", "answer": " jason is not a sissy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " y'know i have dinner plans!!", "answer": " thank you soo much for coming on such a short notice. ladies and gentlemen, i've-i've-i've been practicing medicine for twenty-three years, and i'm stumped.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " okay, this is the den. all right, check this out. lights!  whoa! all right. less lights! bad lights! lights go away!  oh, see you just need to find the right command.", "answer": " yes, and the dimmer switch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " whoa! for a rich guy he's got, that's a pretty small tv.", "answer": " no-no-no, that's a video-phone. but hey guys you're not supposed to be here, so please, do not touch anything.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": "  i-kea! this is comfortable.", "answer": "  this place is amazing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " god, that is the nicest kitchen.", "answer": " i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " no! but it's the nicest kitchen, the refrigerator told me to have a great day.", "answer": " look at this! a millionaire's checkbook.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " i guess that's how.", "answer": " hey monica, how's it going.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " oh it\u0092s umm, good! it's umm, it\u0092s good, just here watering the plants.", "answer": " well don't forget that fiches over there by rachel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": "  ahh... chandler's on the couch!!", "answer": " i see him, you guys are just the worst hiders ever.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": "  hey pete.", "answer": " hi, how ya doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " ahh, pete, the other day when you said you needed to talk, umm, just so i know, is it good news or bad news.", "answer": " oh, it's good news. no, it's definitely good news. hold on a second, i have another call.   hey, how's it going?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " oh no-no-no, it's still me.", "answer": " ah, no it's not. i've got picture-in-picture here.  yeah.  yeah, okay. i'm gonna have to call you back later.  monica? you. i'm gonna have to call you back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " oh, oh, okay umm, so i'll see you soon.", "answer": " okay, i love you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " i love you.", "answer": " i love you, love you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " okay. well, it's good news. it's good news.", "answer": " so, what do you thing the good news is?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " oh my.", "answer": " monica's gonna marry a millionaire!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " hello.", "answer": " and that's pete's mom.  commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " mon you definitely have to make it a theme wedding, and the theme could be, \u0093look how much money we\u0092ve got!\u0094 y'know, i mean you could put, you could put money in-in the invitations! you-you could have like little money place settings. and ah, you could start with a money salad! i mean it\u0092ll be dry, but people will like it.", "answer": " would you stop? we\u0092ve only been going out a couple of weeks, i mean we don\u0092t even know if he\u0092s gonna propose.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " yes, but this is pete. okay? he\u0092s not like other people, on your first date he took you to rome. for most guys that\u0092s like a third or fourth date kinda thing.", "answer": " well if-if that\u0092s what it is, then it\u0092s-it\u0092s crazy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " monica\u0092s right. we\u0092re talking about getting married here. okay? she-she can\u0092t just rush into this.", "answer": " oh please, what do you know! you married a lesbian!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " all right. i gotta go. i have break up with vince.", "answer": " oh, so you\u0092re going with the teacher, huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " yeah, i like vince a lot, y'know? but, it\u0092s just jason\u0092s so sensitive, y'know? and in the long run, i think sensitive it\u0092s just better than having just like a really, really, really nice  butt.   jason! definitely jason! okay, wish me luck!", "answer": " good luck!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " excuse me. umm, is vince here?", "answer": " oh sure. vince?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " wow! i didn\u0092t know you guys actually used those.", "answer": " so, what\u0092s up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " umm, wow. this-this isn\u0092t gonna be easy. umm, i don\u0092t think we should see each other anymore.", "answer": " uh-huh. g-good deal.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " i\u0092m sorry.", "answer": " no-no it\u0092s okay. it\u0092s just that ah, i thought we had something pretty special here. and y'know i-i felt like you were someone i could finally open up to, and\u009a  that there\u0092s so much in me i have to share with you yet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " oh my god, i didn\u0092t\u009a", "answer": "  i\u0092m sorry, i can\u0092t talk. i\u0092m gonna go write in my journal.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": "  i\u0092m telling you, if you want to take care of that thing, you should go to my herbal guy.", "answer": " thank you, but i want to remove it pheebs. i don\u0092t want to make it savory.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " y'know when girls sleep with guys with weird things on their body, they tell their friends about it.", "answer": " gimme this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": "  hi! okay, don\u0092t be mad at me, but i couldn\u0092t resist.", "answer": " brides magazines?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": "  oh, you so would! oh, you should get that anyway.  like for clubbing.", "answer": " it is so weird, i know what i said, but uh, this morning, i was lying in bed i was, i was imagining what it would be like to say yes.  i know it\u0092s a little sudden, and it\u0092s a little rushed, and it\u0092s totally not like me to do something like this, but that doesn\u0092t mean i can\u0092t. right? i mean i\u0092m-i\u0092m crazy about pete, and i know that we want the same things, and when i thought about saying yes, it made me really happy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " hey mon umm, if you do get married, can i bring two guests?", "answer": " you didn\u0092t break up with that fireman?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " no, that was my way of telling you. well, it turns out he\u0092s incredibly sensitive, he keeps a journal and he paints. he even showed me charcoal drawings that he drew of me.", "answer": " wow!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " yeah, well he\u0092d prefer water colors, but y'know, he has easy access to a lot of charcoal.", "answer": " so then, are you going to dump jason?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": "  jason?", "answer": " yeah, come on in.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " so phoebe, you ah, sounded kinda serious on the phone, is ah, is anything wrong?", "answer": " nah-ha!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " you must be ross.", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " listen, i got to tell you i\u0092ve-i\u0092ve never been to a guru before, so...", "answer": " well, relax. if it makes you feel better, i\u0092ve attended some of the finest medical schools in central america. well then, let\u0092s take a look at this skin abnormality of yours.  come on, have a seat.  eeh, huh. as i suspected, it\u0092s a koondis!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " what\u0092s a koondis?", "answer": " i don\u0092t know, what\u0092s a koondis with you?  please, lie down! i\u0092ve got a save that oughta shrink that right up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " i guess it\u0092s worth a try.", "answer": " oh sure, we should see results\u0097whoa!! clearly not the way to go!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " what?! what?!", "answer": " we appear to have angered it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " we?! we angered it?!", "answer": " oh, i think i see the problem. and i\u0092m afraid we\u0092re gonna have to use a much stronger tool.  love.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " oh god!", "answer": "  ross, there is absolutely no way this is going to come off unless you start to\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " ow!!", "answer": " oops.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " what was, what was that?", "answer": " well it\u0092s gone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " what?! how\u0092s that?", "answer": " it got caught on my watch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " ooh, nice.", "answer": " so ah, there was this thing i wanted to talk to you about.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " oh, right! i completely forgot about that.", "answer": " well ah, i\u0092ve been doing a lot of thinking, and i look at my life\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " and i feel like i\u0092ve conquered the business world, and i feel like i\u0092ve conquered the intellectual world, and now i-i have the most beautiful woman in the world.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " wow.", "answer": " there\u0092s one thing missing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " what\u0092s that?", "answer": " it\u0092s time for me to conquer the physical world.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " monica, i want to become  the ultimate fighting champion.", "answer": " you wanna what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " i want to become the ultimate fighting champion! it\u0092s the most intense physical competition in the world, it\u0092s banned in 49 states!", "answer": " what are you talking about?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " okay, my trainer, ho chi, is teaching me a combination of gee koon doe and brazilian street fighting, i\u0092ve even had my own octagon training ring designed.", "answer": " and i suppose you used a ring designer for that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " yeah. monica, i want you there in the front row when i win. i want you close enough to smell the blood. what do you think?", "answer": " my parents will be so happy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": "  hey. i was\u009a", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": "  whoa! hey-hey! what\u0092s going on here? who is this guy?", "answer": " i don\u0092t know, he just started kissing me. get him! get him, vince!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " yeah, okay, i\u0092ve-i\u0092ve been dating both of you, and it\u0092s been really horrible. \u0091cause y'know it\u0092s been a lot of fun, for me. umm, but i-i like you both, and i, and i didn\u0092t know how to chose, so... i\u0092m sorry, i\u0092m just, i\u0092m terrible, i\u0092m a terrible person. i\u0092m terrible.", "answer": " phoebe, phoebe relax, it\u0092s okay. i mean we never said this was exclusive.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " yeah, and neither did we. give yourself a break.", "answer": " really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " yeah. i mean y'know, we haven\u0092t been going out that long. come on, we haven\u0092t even slept together yet. huh.", "answer": " you haven\u0092t?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " you have?", "answer": " well, this is none of my business.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": "  i-i can\u0092t believe this! you-you\u0092ve slept with him?!", "answer": " well, i made you a candle light dinner in the park.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": "  well, that could\u0092ve been really awkward.", "answer": " you made him a candle light dinner in the park?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " yeah, but i-i-i-i can do that for you, i\u0092m gonna do that for you.", "answer": " uh yeah, i can\u0092t believe i ever went out with somebody who would actually have an open flame in the middle of a wooden area.  closing credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": "  everything\u0092s gonna be all right. okay, dick?", "answer": "  hello, i am guru saj--whoa!!  that\u0092s supposed to be a duck right? \u0091cause otherwise, this is waaay out of my league.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " yeah, yeah. he\u0092s got a, he\u0092s got a really bad cough, and our vet, he can\u0092t do anything about it. is there something you can do?", "answer": " hmm, let me see. let me see. do you think you could get him to eat a bat?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}]